# **Garth Hammonds**

Corona, CA 92882 garthbhammonds@gmail.com (951)227-8706

Portfolio: https://hammonds526.github.io/Portfolio

Github: https://github.com/hammonds526

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/garth-hammonds/

#### **Professional Summary:**

I'm a hard working individual, experienced in full-stack web development, customer service, training associates, marketing, graphic design, and project management. I was brought up with a strong code of ethics and morals, as well as a thirst for knowledge. In previous employment, I have been used by multiple departments due to my quick learning, diligent work ethic, and problem solving ability.

#### Proficiencies:

- JavaScript, both in back and front-end development
- Node and Express
- React
- JQuery
- Ajax
- Github
- Heroku
- .NET Framework
- SQL and MongoDB databases along with experience in Mongoose and Sequelize libraries
- NoSOL
- Bootstrap and Bulma CSS styling libraries
- HTML and CSS
- REST
- Experience with C#
- Passport
- · Adobe Photoshop
- Excel
- User Authentication
- Utilizing API's whether local or foreign
- Skilled in team and project management
- Proficient use in Microsoft Excel, Word, and PowerPoint
- Time-stressed assignments

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

# Work Experience

## **Client Services Rep/Senior Customer Service Representative**

Cofiroute USA - Corona, CA November 2017 to Present

- · Trained new employees
- · Assist walk-in guests
- · Answer questions regarding current CA road laws that apply to toll roads and express lanes
- · Follow-up of customer complaints
- · Excellent customer and manager reviews
- · Process incoming customer statements and new customer applications

### **Office Assistant**

Johnny's Auto Color - Riverside, CA March 2016 to November 2017

- · Answered phone calls from Customers and suppliers
- · Welcomed and assisted walk-in guests
- · Inventory of incoming parts
- · Pick-up and drop-off of customer's vehicles
- · Wrote checks for parts and took customer payments

## **Accounting Assistant**

Richgrove Company - Riverside, CA March 2012 to October 2017

- · Invoiced clients
- · Received payments from customers
- · Made deposits
- · Payroll
- · Managed and balanced accounts
- · Created and presented reports
- · Cut checks
- · Copies and filing

#### Real Estate Agent/Realtor

Keller Williams - Corona, CA May 2015 to March 2016

- · Open houses 1-2 times a week
- · Cold calling
- · Practice with purchase agreements and other such contracts

### Marketing Assistant/Graphic Designer/Photographer

TMI Products Inc. - Corona, CA January 2012 to January 2015

- $\cdot \ \text{On-staff photographer}$
- · Helped the marketing director with planning events
- · Designed pamphlets, catalogs, banners, and promotional pages for the website
- · Managed the company's online eBay, Craigslist, and Amazon accounts
- · Helped with merchandise guides for dealers
- · Helped with product up-dates on website forums
- · Took merchandise stock photos to be used for customers and dealers

### **Store Clerk**

Albertsons - Corona, CA

September 2011 to January 2012

- · Deli department
- · Alcohol department
- · General merchandise department
- · Courtesy clerk
- · Assisted bakery, produce, and grocery departments

## Education

# **College Degree in Full-Stack Web Development**

University of California Riverside - Riverside, CA  $2020\ to\ 2021$ 

# Some College in General Studies

Norco College - Norco, CA September 2011 to May 2014

## **High School Diploma**

Corona High School - Corona, CA 2008 to 2011

# Skills

- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- APIs
- Git
- CSS
- SQL
- C#
- HTML5
- MongoDB
- XML
- Authentication
- .NET
- React
- MySQL
- MySQL
- Node.js
- GitHub
- AJAX
- JSON

- Microsoft SQL Server
- REST
- NoSQL
- MVC
- Web Services

### Links

https://github.com/hammonds526

https://hammonds526.github.io/Portfolio

### Assessments

## **Software developer fit — Expert**

July 2021

Measures the traits that are important for successful software developers

Full results: Expert

# Work style: Conscientiousness — Highly Proficient

February 2020

Tendency to be well-organized, rule-abiding, and hard-working.

Full results: <u>Highly Proficient</u>

## Advanced attention to detail — Expert

July 2021

Identifying differences in materials, following instructions, and detecting details among distracting

information

Full results: Expert

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.